{
  "name": "50 Aves Comunes",
  "cost": 5,
  "cards": [
    { "question": "Sparrow", "answer": "Gorrión" },
    { "question": "Pigeon", "answer": "Paloma" },
    { "question": "Eagle", "answer": "Águila" },
    { "question": "Chicken", "answer": "Gallina" },
    { "question": "Duck", "answer": "Pato" },
    { "question": "Goose", "answer": "Ganso" },
    { "question": "Owl", "answer": "Búho" },
    { "question": "Crow", "answer": "Cuervo" },
    { "question": "Robin", "answer": "Petirrojo" },
    { "question": "Swan", "answer": "Cisne" },
    { "question": "Turkey", "answer": "Pavo" },
    { "question": "Penguin", "answer": "Pingüino" },
    { "question": "Hawk", "answer": "Halcón" },
    { "question": "Vulture", "answer": "Buitre" },
    { "question": "Flamingo", "answer": "Flamenco" },
    { "question": "Pelican", "answer": "Pelícano" },
    { "question": "Hummingbird", "answer": "Colibrí" },
    { "question": "Woodpecker", "answer": "Pájaro carpintero" },
    { "question": "Parrot", "answer": "Loro" },
    { "question": "Toucan", "answer": "Tucán" },
    { "question": "Cockatoo", "answer": "Cacatúa" },
    { "question": "Canary", "answer": "Canario" },
    { "question": "Magpie", "answer": "Urraca" },
    { "question": "Starling", "answer": "Estornino" },
    { "question": "Swallow", "answer": "Golondrina" },
    { "question": "Kingfisher", "answer": "Martín pescador" },
    { "question": "Quail", "answer": "Codorniz" },
    { "question": "Pheasant", "answer": "Faisán" },
    { "question": "Ostrich", "answer": "Avestruz" },
    { "question": "Emu", "answer": "Emú" },
    { "question": "Cassowary", "answer": "Casuario" },
    { "question": "Peacock", "answer": "Pavo real" },
    { "question": "Heron", "answer": "Garza" },
    { "question": "Crane", "answer": "Grulla" },
    { "question": "Stork", "answer": "Cigüeña" },
    { "question": "Albatross", "answer": "Albatros" },
    { "question": "Seagull", "answer": "Gaviota" },
    { "question": "Kite", "answer": "Milano" },
    { "question": "Wren", "answer": "Chochín" },
    { "question": "Finch", "answer": "Pinzón" },
    { "question": "Blackbird", "answer": "Mirlo" },
    { "question": "Blue Jay", "answer": "Arrendajo azul" },
    { "question": "Cardinal", "answer": "Cardenal" },
    { "question": "Chickadee", "answer": "Carbonero" },
    { "question": "Mockingbird", "answer": "Sinsonte" },
    { "question": "Thrush", "answer": "Zorzal" },
    { "question": "Nightingale", "answer": "Ruiseñor" },
    { "question": "Warbler", "answer": "Curruca" },
    { "question": "Vireo", "answer": "Vireo" },
    { "question": "Oriole", "answer": "Oriol" }
  ]
}